<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
	<m1 label="MainPage" value="MarketCenter">
<!-- 		<child label="View Order" value="a" textDecoration="none"  fontWeight="bold" fontFamily="Cordia New" fontSize="16"/> -->
	</m1>
	<l1>
		<child label="Vegetables">
         	<child label="Root vegetables" value="0001"/>
			<child label="Stem vegetables" value="0001"/>
			<child label="Ye Cailei" value="0001"/>
			<child label="Cauliflower class" value="0001"/>
			<child label="Fruit vegetables" value="0001"/>
			<child label="Seeds" value="0001"/>
		</child>
		<child label="Fruits">
			<child label="Spring fruit" value="0002"/>
			<child label="Summer fruits" value="0002"/>
			<child label="Autumn fruit" value="0002"/>
			<child label="Winter fruit" value="0002"/>
		</child>
		<child label="Grain">
			<child label="Wheat" value="0003"/>
			<child label="Unhusked rice" value="0003"/>
			<child label="Corn" value="0003"/>
			<child label="Millet" value="0003"/>
		</child>
		<child label="Bean Products">
			<child label="Soybean" value="0004"/>
			<child label="Broad bean" value="0004"/>
			<child label="Pea" value="0004"/>
			<child label="Mung bean" value="0004"/>
			<child label="Red adzuki beans" value="0004"/>
			<child label="Kidney bean" value="0004"/>
		</child>
		<child label="Wheat">
			<child label="Barley" value="0005"/>
			<child label="Oat" value="0005"/>
			<child label="Rye" value="0005"/>
			<child label="Indica rice" value="0005"/>
			<child label="Japonica rice" value="0005"/>
			<child label="Nuo rice" value="0005"/>
		</child>
		<child label="Meat">
			<child label="Pork" value="0006"/>
			<child label="Beef" value="0006"/>
			<child label="Mutton" value="0006"/>
			<child label="Chicken" value="0006"/>
			<child label="Duck" value="0006"/>
			<child label="Flesh of a donkey" value="0006"/>
		</child>
	</l1>
	<h1>
	Digo shopping website user registration protocol
	
	This agreement is you and Digo mall site (referred to as "the station") owner (hereinafter referred to as the "Digo mall") between the Digo mall site services and other matters relating to a contract, please carefully read the license agreement, you click the "agree to these terms, identified" button, this Agreement constitutes binding on the parties legal documents.

Article first the confirmation and acceptance of terms
	The 1.1 station of the electronic services right to the ownership and operation of all Digo mall. The user agrees to all registered the terms of the agreement and the completion of the registration process, to become the station 's official users. User confirmation: the terms and conditions of this agreement is dealing with the rights and obligations of both parties of contract, always effective, otherwise mandatory provisions of law or the Parties otherwise specifically agreed, in accordance with the provisions of.
	1.2 user click agree this agreement, as the user confirmation is to enjoy the service station, shopping, place an order corresponding to the power and capacity, can bear legal liability independently.
	1.3 if you are under the age of 18, you can only to parents or guardians guardianship involvement can use this station.
	1.4digo mall is retained in the mainland people's Republic of China law enforcement within the limits permitted by law alone determined denial of service, user account, remove or edit the content or the right of cancellation.

Article second the station services
	2.1digo mall via the Internet to provide users with internet information services, users in complete agreement and the station set of circumstances, is entitled to use the station services.
	2.2 user must prepare the following equipment and undertake the following expenses: (1) online equipment, including but not limited to the computer or other Internet terminals, modems and other necessary Internet device; (2) Internet expenses, including but not limited to Internet access fees, Internet equipment rental, mobile phone traffic fees.

Third user information
	3.1 users should be honest to the registration information, the user agrees to provide registration information true, accurate, complete, valid, the user registration information such as change, should renew its registration information. If the user provides registration information is not legitimate, untrue, inaccurate, incomplete, users must bear the consequences and responsibilities, and the Digo store retains an end user using Digo mall services right.
	The 3.2 user browsing, place an order at this station, shopping and other activities, involving the user real name/name, address, telephone, e-mail and other private information, this station will be strictly confidential, unless the user is authorized or otherwise stipulated by law, the station won't disclose user privacy.
	3.3 user registration is successful, will produce a username and password and other account information, you can according to the provisions of this station to change your password. Users should be cautious and reasonable storage, using their username and password. The user if any illegal use of user account or the presence of security vulnerabilities, please immediately notify the station and to report to the public security organs.
	3.4 user consent, Digo mall has through the mail, telephone and other forms, to the station, shopping, registered users to consignees and order information, promotion activities and to inform information rights.
	The 3.5 user may not be the registration account to lend to others, otherwise the user shall bear all responsibilities arising from actual use, and people assume joint responsibility.
	3.6 user consent, Digo mall have the right to use the user registration, user name, password and other information, access to user account registration, for preservation of evidence, including but not limited to the notary, witness.

Fourth user in accordance with the law and obligation
	This agreement according to national relevant laws and regulations on formulation of rules and regulations, the user agrees to comply strictly with the following duties:
	(1) may not transfer or published: incitement to resist, the destruction of the Constitution and the laws, administrative rules and regulations the implementation of speech, inciting subversion of state power, overthrow the socialist system utterances, inciting the split of the country, and undermining national unity of speech, incite ethnic hatred, discrimination, and undermining national unity of speech;
	(2) from the Chinese mainland to exit transfer information must conform to the relevant Chinese laws and regulations;
	(3) the use of this site may not engage in money laundering, stealing commercial secrets, to steal personal information and other illegal and criminal activities;
	(4) may not interfere with the normal operation, not to trespass the station and the national computer information system;
	(5) may not transfer or publication of any crime, sexual harassment, slander others, abusive, threatening, nociceptive, vulgar, obscene, indecent and other information;
	(6) may not transfer or published damage national social public interest and relates to national security information or comments;
	(7) of this article shall not instigate others engaged in prohibited behavior;
	(8) may use the station registered account profit business activities;
	(9) shall not publish any copyright infringement, trademark and other intellectual property rights or legal rights;
	The user should often pay close attention to and comply with the station as published from time to time or modification of the various types of legal rules.
	The station retains the delete station various does not conform to the legal policy or untrue information content without notifying the user rights.
	If the user does not comply with the above rules, this site has the right to make independent judgments and take the suspension or closure of user accounts and other measures. Users need to be on their own in the online speech and behavior assume legal responsibility.

Article fifth the commodity information
	The station's commodity price, quantity, whether goods such as commodity information at any time may change, the station does not make special notice. Because the website the commodity information is enormous, although the station will make the greatest efforts to ensure your browsing goods information accuracy, as everyone knows but due to the Internet technology factors of objective reasons, the station webpage display information may have a certain lag error, this situation you know and understand the Digo mall welcome; error correction, and will be given a reward for error correction.
	The facilities, goods and services referred to as a " commodity " or " goods ".

Sixth order
	6.1 in your order, please confirm the purchase of goods, price, quantity, name of models, specifications, size, contact address, telephone, the consignee information. The consignee and the user himself inconsistent, consignee's behavior and intention as the user's behavior and intention, the user response to the consignee's behavior and the legal consequences of the meaning representation are jointly and severally liable.
	6.2 unless otherwise mandatory provisions, both sides agreed as follows: the station sales display of goods and price information is merely an invitation to offer, you must fill in place an order when you want to buy the goods quantity, price and payment, the consignee, contact, delivery address ( performance place of contract performance way of contract, etc.) content; system generated order information computer information system based on your information is generated automatically from the data, only your sales contract offer to Party; sales receipt of your order information, only in the sales side will you in the order form order goods from the warehouse actually sent you ( when to commodity database for mark), side as you and sales between actual direct sent you the goods to establish a contractual relationship; if you are in an order in order a variety of commodity and sale side only sent you some of the goods, you and sales between only actual direct to send you the goods establishment of a contractual relationship; only in the sales of real to you directly sent orders for other goods, you and the sales order in the other between actual straight Then sent you the goods until the establishment of the contract relationship. You can feel free to visit you in this account, check your order status.
	6.3 because of changes in the market and all kinds of reasonable commercial efforts to control factors, the station can not guarantee you submit the order information in the hope that the goods will have the goods; if you plan to purchase goods, shortage, you have the right to cancel the order.

The seventh distribution
	Sales of the 7.1 party will take the goods ( goods ) to you specify the delivery address, all in this station listed on the delivery time is the reference time, the reference time is calculated according to the inventory, the normal process and delivery time, delivery location estimation based on the.
	7.2 due to the following circumstances caused by the order delay or failure in distribution, sales shall not bear responsibility for delayed delivery:
	(1) the information provided by user error, the detailed address and other causes;
	(2) the goods are delivered after no sign for, lead to the delivery or delayed delivery;
	(3) to change the situation factors;
	(4) to force majeure factors, such as: natural disasters, transportation of martial law, war and other emergencies.

Article eighth ownership and intellectual property
	8.1 once the user acceptance of this agreement, that indicate that the user at any time to be published in this station of any form of information content ( including but not limited to customer evaluation, customer consultation, various topics such as the information content ) of the property rights of any transfer of rights, such as property rights ( including copyright is not limited to:copy right, right of distribution, rental rights, right of exhibition, performance rights, rights to show, broadcast rights, the right of information network dissemination, film rights, the right of adaptation, translation, compilation of rights and the right to be enjoyed by copyright owners and other transferable rights), all exclusive and irrevocably transfer to all users agree to the Digo Digo mall, mall has the right infringement of any of the main separate proceedings.
	8.2 this Agreement have constituted a " people's Republic of China Copyright Law " article twenty-fifth ( serial number of articles according to the 2011 edition of copyright law and relevant laws and regulations to determine ) works property rights transfer agreement in writing, its effectiveness and user in Digo shopping website published any works protected by the copyright law, no matter the content of formation on the present agreement entered into before or after the conclusion of the agreement.
	8.3 user consent and have a full understanding of the terms of this agreement, promising not to have been published on the site information, publish in any form or other body authorized by any means available ( including but not limited to the various sites, media use).
	8.4digo mall is the site of the producers, with the website contents and resources of the copyright and other legal rights, legal protection by the state, has the power from time to time to this Agreement and modify the contents of the station, and the station posted, without further notification user. The maximum permitted by law within the mall, Digo of this Agreement and the content has the right to interpret.
	8.5 unless otherwise mandatory provisions, without explicit written permission of Digo mall in particular, any unit or individual shall not in any way illegally copied in whole or in part, reprint, references, links, crawl or otherwise use the station information content, otherwise, Digo mall has right to pursue its legal responsibility.
	In 8.6 the station contains information ( such as text, charts, label, button icons, images, sound files, fragment, digital download, data editing and software ), is Digo mall or its content provider property, by the China International Copyright protection. The station of all content is compiled by Digo store exclusive property, by the China International Copyright protection. The station of all software is Digo mall or its Associate Company or its software provider property, by the China International Copyright protection.

Article ninth liability limitation and does not guarantee
	Unless otherwise expressly written instructions, the station and its containing or otherwise provided through this site to your full information, content, materials, products and services ( including software ), are in the "as is " and " as available " basis provides.
	Unless otherwise expressly written in Digo mall, the station operation and is included in the information on this web site, content, material, products ( including software ) or service of any form, explicit or implicit representations or warranties ( according to the people's Republic of China Law otherwise provided ).
	Digo mall does not guarantee the station contained in or otherwise provided through this site to your full information, content, materials, products and services ( including software ), the server or from the station to send electronic mail, information is free of viruses or other harmful components.
	As a result of force majeure or any other cause beyond the control of the station to this station sales system crash or normal use leads to online transactions can not be completed or loss of relevant information and records, Digo mall will be reasonable efforts to help deal with the aftermath.

Tenth protocol to update and user attention obligation
	According to the national laws and regulations change and site operation needs, Digo mall has the right to modify the terms of this agreement from time to time, the revised agreement once it is posted on this site that the effect, and to replace the original agreement. The user can login access to the latest agreement; users have the obligation to pay close attention to and read the latest version of the agreement and the website announcement. If the user does not agree with the updated protocol, can and should be stopped immediately accept Digo mall site according to the agreement to provide the services; such as users continue to use the services provided by this website, deemed to update protocol. Digo mall recommend in the use of the station prior to the reading of this Agreement and the station announcement. If this agreement to any one regarded as invalid or abolished, for any reason not executable, it shall be deemed to be divided and does not affect any other provision of the validity and enforceability.

Article eleventh the legal jurisdiction and Application
	The formation of this agreement, implementation and interpretation and dispute settlement should be applied in the mainland people's Republic of China apply effective laws ( but not including its conflict of laws rules). Such as the occurrence of this Agreement and the applicable law conflict, these articles will be completely in accordance with the law to explain, and other effective shall continue in force. If the parties on the contents of this agreement or its implementation has any dispute, both parties shall attempt to resolve through friendly consultation; consultation fails, either party may apply to the jurisdiction of the people's Republic of China mainland District court.

Twelfth other
	12.1digo mall site owner is referred to in the government sector lawfully permitted or filing of the Digo mall site management main body.
	12.2digo mall to respect users and consumers legitimate rights, this Agreement and the website issued various types of rules, statement and other content, are in order to better, more convenient for users and consumers to provide services. The station to welcome customers and the community to put forward opinions and suggestions, Digo mall will humbly accept and amend this Agreement and the station on the types of rules.
	12.3 this agreement content in bold, bold, italic, underline, remarkable marking articles, please read the user focus.
	12.4 you click on this agreement at the top of the " agreed to the following agreement, defining " button as you fully accept this agreement, before clicking ask you again to confirm known and fully understand this agreement all the content.
	</h1>
</root>